<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<schemalist>
  <schema path='/desktop/gnome/remote-access/' id='org.gnome.Vino'>
    <key type='b' name='enabled'>
      <summary>Enable remote access to the desktop</summary>
      <description>If true, allows remote access to the desktop via the RFB protocol. Users on remote machines may then connect to the desktop using a VNC viewer.</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='prompt-enabled'>
      <summary>Prompt the user before completing a connection</summary>
      <description>If true, remote users accessing the desktop are not allowed access until the user on the host machine approves the connection. Recommended especially when access is not password protected.</description>
      <default>true</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='view-only'>
      <summary>Only allow remote users to view the desktop</summary>
      <description>If true, remote users accessing the desktop are only allowed to view the desktop. Remote users will not be able to use the mouse or keyboard.</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>

    <key type='s' name='network-interface'>
      <summary>Network interface for listening</summary>
      <description>If not set, the server will listen on all network interfaces. Set this if you want that accept connections only from some specific network interface. eg: eth0, wifi0, lo, ...</description>
      <default>''</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='use-alternative-port'>
      <summary>Listen on an alternative port</summary>
      <description>If true, the server will listen to another port, instead of the default (5900). The port must be specified in the 'alternative-port' key.</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>

    <key type='q' name='alternative-port'>
      <summary>Alternative port number</summary>
      <description>The port which the server will listen to if the 'use-alternative-port' key is set to true. Valid values are in the range from 5000 to 50000.</description>
      <default>5900</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='require-encryption'>
      <summary>Require encryption</summary>
      <description>If true, remote users accessing the desktop are required to support encryption. It is highly recommended that you use a client which supports encryption unless the intervening network is trusted.</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>

    <key type='as' name='authentication-methods'>
      <summary>Allowed authentication methods</summary>
      <description>Lists the authentication methods with which remote users may access the desktop. There are two possible authentication methods; "vnc" causes the remote user to be prompted for a password (the password is specified by the vnc-password key) before connecting and "none" which allows any remote user to connect.</description>
      <choices>
        <choice value='none'/>
        <choice value='vnc'/>
      </choices>
      <default>['none']</default>
    </key>

    <key type='s' name='vnc-password'>
      <summary>Password required for "vnc" authentication</summary>
      <description>The password which the remote user will be prompted for if the "vnc" authentication method is used. The password specified by the key is base64 encoded. The special value of 'keyring' (which is not valid base64) means that the password is stored in the GNOME keyring.</description>
      <default>'keyring'</default>
    </key>

    <key type='s' name='mailto'>
      <summary>E-mail address to which the remote desktop URL should be sent</summary>
      <description>This key specifies the e-mail address to which the remote desktop URL should be sent if the user clicks on the URL in the Desktop Sharing preferences dialog.</description>
      <default>''</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='lock-screen-on-disconnect'>
      <summary>Lock the screen when last user disconnect</summary>
      <description>If true, screen will be locked after the last remote client disconnect.</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>

    <key name='icon-visibility' enum="org.gnome.Vino.VinoIconVisibility">
      <summary>When the status icon should be shown</summary>
      <description>This key controls the behavior of the status icon. There are three options: "always" - The icon will be always there; "client" - You will see the icon only when there is someone connected, this is the default behavior; "never" - Never shows the icon.</description>
      <default>'client'</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='disable-background'>
      <summary>When true, disable the background on receive valid session</summary>
      <description>When true, disable the background on receive valid session</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='use-upnp'>
      <summary>Whether we should use UPNP to forward the port in routers</summary>
      <description>If true, we will use UPNP protocol to automatically forward the port used by vino in the router.</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>

    <key type='b' name='disable-xdamage'>
      <summary>Whether we should disable the XDamage extension of X.org</summary>
      <description>If true, we will not use the XDamage extension of X.org. This extension does not work properly on some video drivers when using 3D effects. Disabling it will make vino work on these environments with a slower rendering as side effect.</description>
      <default>false</default>
    </key>
  </schema>
</schemalist>