<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<audio-profiles>
  <profiles>
    <profile id="flac">
      <name>Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="ar">المرماز الحر غير الفاقد للصوت</name>
      <name xml:lang="ast">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="be@latin">Svabodny kodek aŭdyjo biaz strataŭ jakaści (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="bg">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="br">FLAC</name>
      <name xml:lang="ca">Còdec lliure d'àudio sense pèrdua (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Còdec lliure d'àudio sense pèrdua (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="cs">Svobodný bezeztrátový zvukový kodek</name>
      <name xml:lang="da">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="de">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="dz">རང་དབང་གྱོང་མེད་རྣར་ཉེན་ཀོ་ཌེཀ་</name>
      <name xml:lang="el">Ελεύθερος Μη Απωλεστικός Κωδικοποιητής Ήχου (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="en_GB">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="eo">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="es">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="eu">Galerarik gabeko audio-kodek librea</name>
      <name xml:lang="fi">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="fr">FLAC (Free Lossless Audio Codec)</name>
      <name xml:lang="gl">Códec de son libre sen pérdida</name>
      <name xml:lang="gu">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="he">מקודד שמע חופשי ללא אבדן איכות (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="hu">Szabad veszteségmentes hangkodek (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="it">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="ja">FLAC(Free Lossless Audio Codec)</name>
      <name xml:lang="ko">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="ky">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="lt">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="lv">Brīvs bezzudumu audio kodeks</name>
      <name xml:lang="mk">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="nl">Vrije Audio-codec zonder kwaliteitsverlies (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="pa">ਮੁਫ਼ਤ ਲਾਸਲੈਸ ਆਡੀਓ ਕੋਡਿੰਗ</name>
      <name xml:lang="pl">FLAC</name>
      <name xml:lang="pt">Codec de Áudio Free Lossless</name>
      <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Free Lossless Audio Codec - "Codec livre de áudio sem perdas"</name>
      <name xml:lang="ro">Codec audio fără pierderi gratuit</name>
      <name xml:lang="ru">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="sl">Brezplačni kodek za kodiranje brez zvočnih izgub (FLAC)</name>
      <name xml:lang="sr">Слободни кодек без губитка</name>
      <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Slobodni kodek bez gubitka</name>
      <name xml:lang="sv">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="tr">Özgür Kayıpsız Ses Kodlayıcı</name>
      <name xml:lang="uk">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="vi">Free Lossless Audio Codec</name>
      <name xml:lang="zh_CN">自由无损音频编码解码器</name>
      <name xml:lang="zh_HK">無損音頻壓縮編碼</name>
      <name xml:lang="zh_TW">無損音頻壓縮編碼</name>
      <description>Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) is an open source codec that compresses but does not degrade audio quality.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ar">المرماز الحر غير الفاقد للصوت (FLAC) هو مرماز مفتوح المصدر يقوم بضغط الصوت دون التأثير على جودته.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ast">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC, códec de soníu llibre y ensin perda) ye un códec de códigu abiertu que comprime pero nun degrada la calidá del soníu.</description>
      <description xml:lang="be@latin">Svabodny kodek aŭdyjo biaz strataŭ jakaści (FLAC) - heta kodek z adkrytymi kryničnymi kodami, jaki ŭžyvaje kampresiju, ale nie źmianšaje jakaści huku.</description>
      <description xml:lang="bg">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) е кодек с отворен код, който компресира, но не намалява качеството. </description>
      <description xml:lang="ca">El còdec lliure d'àudio sense pèrdua (FLAC) és un còdec de codi obert que comprimeix sense degradar la qualitat de l'àudio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ca@valencia">El còdec lliure d'àudio sense pèrdua (FLAC) és un còdec de codi obert que comprimeix sense degradar la qualitat de l'àudio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="cs">Svobodný bezeztrátový zvukový kodek (FLAC) je otevřený kodek využívající komprimaci beze ztráty kvality zvuku.</description>
      <description xml:lang="da">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) er et åbent format som komprimerer uden at forringe lydkvaliteten.</description>
      <description xml:lang="de">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) ist ein quelloffener Codec, der komprimiert, aber die Audioqualität nicht verschlechtert.</description>
      <description xml:lang="dz">རང་དབང་གྱོང་མེད་རྣར་ཉེན་ཀོ་ཌེཀ་ (FLAC) འདི་  ཨེབ་བཙུགས་འབད་མི་ཨིན་དེ་འབདཝ་ད་རྣར་ཉེན་སྤུས་ཚད་ཉམས་འགྱོ་ནི་མེད་པའི་བྱུང་ཁུངས་ཁ་ཕྱེ་བཏུབ་མི་འདི་ཨིན།</description>
      <description xml:lang="el">Ο ελεύθερος μη απωλεστικός κωδικοποιητής ήχου (FLAC) είναι ένας κωδικοποιητής ανοιχτού κώδικα που συμπιέζει αλλά δεν υποβαθμίζει την ποιότητα του ήχου.</description>
      <description xml:lang="en_GB">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) is an open source codec that compresses but does not degrade audio quality.</description>
      <description xml:lang="eo">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) estas malfermitkoda sonkodeko, kiu densigas sed ne malaltigas sonkvaliton.</description>
      <description xml:lang="es">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC, códec de sonido libre y sin pérdida) es un códec de código abierto que comprime pero no degrada la calidad del sonido.</description>
      <description xml:lang="eu">Galerarik gabeko audio-kodek librea (GGAKL) iturburu irekiko kodek bat da, eta audioa konprimitzen du kalitatea galdu gabe.</description>
      <description xml:lang="fi">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) on avoimen lähdekoodin koodekki, joka pakkaa, mutta ei alenna äänen laatua.</description>
      <description xml:lang="fr">Le codec FLAC (Free Lossless Audio Codec) est un codec Open Source qui compresse sans dégrader la qualité audio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="gl">O códec de son libre e sen pérdida (FLAC) é un códec de fonte aberta que comprime pero non degrada a calidade do son.</description>
      <description xml:lang="gu">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) એ ઓપન સોર્સ કોડેક છે કે જે સંકોચન કરે છે પરંતુ ઓડિયોની ગુણવત્તા ઘટાડતું નથી.</description>
      <description xml:lang="he">מקודד שמע חופשי ללא אבדן נתונים (FLAC) הנו מקודד בקוד פתוח שדוחס או לא מוריד באיכות השמע.</description>
      <description xml:lang="hu">A Szabad veszteségmentes hangkodek (FLAC) egy nyílt forrású kodek, amely tömörít, de nem rontja a hangminőséget.</description>
      <description xml:lang="it">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) è un formato Open Source che comprime ma non degrada la qualità audio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ja">FLACはオープンソースのコーデックです。可逆圧縮ですので音質を劣化させません。</description>
      <description xml:lang="ko">FLAC(Free Lossless Audio Codec)는 오픈 소스 코덱으로, 압축할 때 오디오 품질을 저하시키지 않습니다.</description>
      <description xml:lang="lt">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) yra atvirojo kodo kodekas, glaudinantis, tačiau nemažinantis garso kokybės.</description>
      <description xml:lang="lv">Brīvs bezzudumu audio kodeks (FLAC) ir atvērtā pirmkoda kodeks, kurš saspiež, bet nebojā audio kvalitāti.</description>
      <description xml:lang="mk">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) е слободен кодек кој компресира но не го намалува квалитетот на звуккот.</description>
      <description xml:lang="nl">De Vrije Audio-codec zonder kwaliteitsverlies (FLAC) is een open-source codec die wel comprimeert maar geen kwaliteits verlies oplevert.</description>
      <description xml:lang="pa">ਫਰੀ ਲੂਜਲੈੱਸ ਆਡੀਓ ਕੋਡ (FLAC) ਇੱਕ ਓਪਨ ਸੋਰਸ ਕੋਡਕ ਹੈ, ਜੋ ਕਿ ਕੰਪਰੈੱਸਡ ਹੈ, ਪਰ ਆਡੀਓ ਕੁਆਲਟੀ ਡੀਗਰੇਡ ਨਹੀਂ ਕਰਦਾ ਹੈ।</description>
      <description xml:lang="pl">FLAC, (Free Lossless Audio Codec) to dostępny na wolnej, otwartej licencji kodek, umożliwiający bezstratną kompresję dźwięku.</description>
      <description xml:lang="pt">O Codec de Áudio Free Lossless (FLAC) é um codec de código aberto que comprime mas não degrada a qualidade do áudio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="pt_BR">O Codec livre de áudio sem perdas - "Free Lossless Audio Codec" (FLAC) é um codec de código aberto que comprime mas não degrada a qualidade de áudio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ro">Codec audio fără pierderi gratuit (FLAC) este un codec open source care comprimă, dar nu degradează calitatea audio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ru">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) — кодек с открытым исходным кодом, сжимающий звуковые данные без потери качества.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sl">Brezplačni kodek za kodiranje brez zvočnih izgub (FLAC) je odprtokodni kodek, ki zvok stisne, vendar ne poslabša njegove kakovosti.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sr">ФЛАЦ је слободан звучни кодек који смањује величину датотека без губитка на квалитету.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sr@latin">FLAC je slobodan zvučni kodek koji smanjuje veličinu datoteka bez gubitka na kvalitetu.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sv">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) är en kodek med öppen källkod som komprimerar utan att minska på ljudkvaliteten.</description>
      <description xml:lang="tr">Özgür Kayıpsız Ses Kodlayıcı (FLAC), sıkıştıran ama ses kalitesini düşürmeyen bir açık kaynaklı bir kodlamadır.</description>
      <description xml:lang="uk">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) — це вільний кодек, що стискає, але не погіршує якість аудіо.</description>
      <description xml:lang="vi">Free Lossless Audio Codec (FLAC) là chuẩn mã hóa mở, dùng để nén âm thanh mà không ảnh hưởng nhiều đến chất lượng.</description>
      <description xml:lang="zh_CN">自由无损音频编码解码器(FLAC)是一个开源编码解码器格式，能够进行压缩而不降低音频质量。</description>
      <description xml:lang="zh_HK">無損音訊壓縮編碼 (FLAC) 是一項開放源碼的編解碼格式，它並不會降低音樂的品質。</description>
      <description xml:lang="zh_TW">無損音訊壓縮編碼 (FLAC) 是一項開放源碼的編解碼格式，它並不會降低音樂的品質。</description>
      <output-file-extension>flac</output-file-extension>
      <mimetype>application/x-flac</mimetype>
      <mimetype>audio/flac</mimetype>
      <mimetype>audio/x-flac</mimetype>
      <mimetype>taglib/flac</mimetype>
      <pipeline>
        <process id="gstreamer">
        <![CDATA[
            (gst-construct-pipeline 
                "audioconvert" 
                "flacenc")
        ]]>
        </process>
      </pipeline>
    </profile>
  </profiles>
</audio-profiles>