<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<audio-profiles>
  <profiles>
    <profile id="wav">
      <name>Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ast">Forma de onda PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="be@latin">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="bg">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ca">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ca@valencia">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="cs">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="da">Bølgeform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="de">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="dz">གཡབ་རྣམ་པ་ པི་སི་ཨེམ་</name>
      <name xml:lang="el">Κυματομορφή PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="en_GB">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="eo">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="es">Forma de onda PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="eu">Waveform PKM</name>
      <name xml:lang="fi">PCM-aaltomuoto</name>
      <name xml:lang="fr">Onde PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="gl">Forma de onda PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="gu">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="he">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="hu">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="it">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ja">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ko">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ky">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="lt">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="lv">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="mk">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="nl">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="pa">ਵੇਵਫਾਰਮ PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="pl">Przebieg PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="pt">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="pt_BR">Forma de onda PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ro">Formă de undă PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="ru">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="sl">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="sr">Вејвформ ПЦМ</name>
      <name xml:lang="sr@latin">Vejvform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="sv">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="tr">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="uk">Waveform PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="zh_CN">声波形式的 PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="zh_HK">波形 PCM</name>
      <name xml:lang="zh_TW">波形 PCM</name>
      <description>WAV+PCM is a lossless format that holds uncompressed, raw pulse-code modulated (PCM) audio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ast">WAV+PCM ye un formatu ensin perda que caltién soníu non comprimíu en modulación de pulsos codificaos (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="be@latin">WAV+PCM - heta farmat biaz strataŭ jakaści, jaki ŭtrymlivaje nieskampresavany, suvory, zmadulavany ŭ puls-kod (PCM) huk.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ca">El WAV+PCM és un format sense pèrdua no comprimit que conté àudio modulat (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="ca@valencia">El WAV+PCM és un format sense pèrdua no comprimit que conté àudio modulat (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="cs">WAV+PCM je bezeztrátový formát obsahující nekomprimovaný surový zvuk s pulzně kódovou modulací (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="da">WAV+PCM er et ikke-forringende format som indeholder ukomprimeret, rå pulskodemoduleret (PCM) lyd.</description>
      <description xml:lang="de">WAV+PCM ist ein verlustfreies Format, das unkomprimierte, roh kodiert modulierte Audioinformation (PCM) speichert.</description>
      <description xml:lang="dz">WAV+PCM འདི་  ཚད་གཞི་(པི་སི་ཨེམ་)རྣར་ཉེན་འཆང་མི་ ཨེབ་བཙུགས་མ་འབད་མི་  གྲལ་ཐིག་འཕར་རྩ་-ཨང་ཚད་རྩི་འདི་ཨིན།</description>
      <description xml:lang="el">Το WAV+PCM είναι μία μη απωλεστική μορφή που διατηρεί μη συμπιεσμένο, ακατέργαστο ήχο, παλμοκωδικής διαμόρφωσης (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="en_GB">WAV+PCM is a lossless format that holds uncompressed, raw pulse-code modulated (PCM) audio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="eo">WAV+PCM estas senperda formo kiu entenas nedensigitan, krudan pulskode modulitan sonon (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="es">WAV+PCM es un formato sin pérdida que contiene sonido no comprimido en modulación de pulsos codificados (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="eu">WAV+PCM galerarik gabeko formatua da, pultsu kodetuen bidez modulatutako (PKM) konprimitu gabeko audio gordina duena.</description>
      <description xml:lang="fi">WAV+PCM-muoto pitää sisällään pakkaamatonta, raakaa Pulse-Code Modulated (PCM) -ääntä.</description>
      <description xml:lang="fr">WAV + PCM est un format sans perte qui contient de l'audio brut modulé (PCM) sans compression.</description>
      <description xml:lang="gl">WAV+PCM é un formato de ficheiro con pérdida que mantén o son sen compresión, con modulación de pulsos codificados.</description>
      <description xml:lang="gu">WAV+PCM એ નષ્ટવીહિન બંધારણ છે કે જે વિસંકોચન, કાચો pulse-code modulated (PCM) ઓડિયો સાચવે છે.</description>
      <description xml:lang="he">WAV+PCM הנו מבנה קובץ ללא אובן נתונים המחזיק שמע בלתי דחוס ובעל מודולציית קוד מתקפים (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="hu">A Wav+PCM egy tömörítetlen, nyers impulzuskód-modulált (PCM) hangot tároló veszteségmentes formátum.</description>
      <description xml:lang="it">WAV+PCM è un formato senza nessun tipo di perdita che contiene audio grezzo non compresso, con modulazione pulse-code (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="ja">WAV+PCMは圧縮されていないPCMデータを保持するフォーマットです。</description>
      <description xml:lang="ko">WAV+PCM은 압축하지 않은 원본 PCM (펄스 부호 변조) 오디오가 들어 있는 무손실 형식입니다.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ky">WAV+PCM сапаттуу, маалыматтарды кысуусуз сактоочу, пульстук-коддук модуляциясы менен болгон формат болуп саналат.</description>
      <description xml:lang="lt">WAV+PCM yra nenuostolingas formatas, saugantis neglaudintą, neapdorotą vibracijų kodu moduliuotą (PCM) garsą. </description>
      <description xml:lang="lv">WAV+PCM ir bezzudumu audio formāts, kurš satur nekompresētu pulse-code modulated (PCM) audio.</description>
      <description xml:lang="mk">WAV+PCM е незагублив формат кој содржи некомпресирано, сирово pulse-code модулирано (PCM) аудио.</description>
      <description xml:lang="nl">WAV+PCM is a een formaat zonder kwaliteitsverlies dat niet-gecomprimeerde, ‘pulse-code modulated’-geluid (PCM) bevat.</description>
      <description xml:lang="pa">WAV+PCM ਇੱਕ ਲੂਜ਼ਲੈੱਸ ਫਾਰਮੈਟ ਹੈ, ਜੋ ਕਿ ਅਣ-ਕੰਪਰੈੱਸਡ, ਰਾਅ ਪਲੱਸ-ਕੋਡ ਮੋਡੀਉਲਟਡ (PCM) ਆਡੀਓ ਹੈ।</description>
      <description xml:lang="pl">WAV+PCM to bezstratny format przechowujący dźwięk za pomocą modulacji pulsowo-kodowej (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="pt">WAV+PCM é um formato de codificação sem perda que contém áudio de código de pulsos modulado (PCM) em bruto.</description>
      <description xml:lang="pt_BR">WAV+PCM é um formato de perda reduzida que contém áudio de modulação de código de pulso (PCM) descomprimido.</description>
      <description xml:lang="ro">WAV + PCM este un format fără pierderi care reține necomprimate, pulsuri audio modulate neprocesate în cod (PCM).</description>
      <description xml:lang="ru">WAV+PCM — формат без потери качества, хранит данные без сжатия в импульсно-кодовой модуляции.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sl">Oblika zapisa WAV+PCM je kodirana brez zvočnih izgub in vsebuje nestisnjen, surov pulzirajoče-kodno moduliran (PCM) zvok.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sr">ВАВ+ПЦМ је формат без губитака који чува несажети, изворни импулсним кодом модулисани (ПЦМ) звук.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sr@latin">VAV+PCM je format bez gubitaka koji čuva nesažeti, izvorni impulsnim kodom modulisani (PCM) zvuk.</description>
      <description xml:lang="sv">WAV+PCM är ett icke-förstörande format som innehåller okomprimerat, rå pulskodsmodulerat (PCM) ljud.</description>
      <description xml:lang="tr">WAV+PCM sıkıştırılmamış şekilde tutan kayıpsız bir biçimdir, vuruş kodu örneklemeli (PCM) ham ses. </description>
      <description xml:lang="uk">WAV+PCM — це формат без втрат, що зберігається нестисненим, сира імпульснокодова модуляція (ІКМ) звуку.</description>
      <description xml:lang="vi">WAV+PCM là một định dạng không tổn hao, chứa âm thanh mô phỏng sóng rung thô, chưa được nén.</description>
      <description xml:lang="zh_CN">WAV+PCM 是一个无损的格式，保存未压缩的原始脉冲码的调制(PCM)音频。</description>
      <description xml:lang="zh_HK">WAV+PCM 是一種無失真格式，保存了未壓縮、原始的脈衝編碼調變 (PCM) 音訊。</description>
      <description xml:lang="zh_TW">WAV+PCM 是一種無失真格式，保存了未壓縮、原始的脈衝編碼調變 (PCM) 音訊。</description>
      <output-file-extension>wav</output-file-extension>
      <mimetype>audio/x-wav</mimetype>
      <mimetype>audio/wav</mimetype>
      <pipeline>
        <process id="gstreamer">
        <![CDATA[
            (gst-construct-pipeline
                "audioresample"
                "audioconvert" 
                (+ "audio/x-raw-int, "
                   "endianness=(int)1234, "
                   "width=(int)16, "
                   "depth=(int)16, "
                   "signed=(boolean)true, "
                   "rate=(int)44100, "
                   "channels=(int)2" )
                "wavenc")
        ]]>
        </process>
      </pipeline>
    </profile>
  </profiles>
</audio-profiles>